amfiindia.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy Notice | Mutual Funds in India | Equity Mutual Funds

Thank you for visiting [www.amfiindia.com.](http://www.amfiindia.com/) We at AMFI respect your privacy and consider it an important element of our service. Our privacy policy is straightforward: We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website unless you volunteer to provide that information to us. This is broadly how we handle the information we gather.

#### Information Collected and Stored Automatically

If you visit our website just to browse, read pages or download information, we gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information cannot and does not identify you personally.

The kind of information that is gathered automatically include the type of browser you are using (e.g. Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), the type of Operating System you are using (e.g. Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. America Online, Satyam Online, Mantra Online, VSNL), the date and time of your visit and the pages you visit. We sometimes use this non-personally identifiable information to improve our website(s) design, content and primarily to give you a better browsing experience.

#### Links to Other Sites

Our website sometimes has links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) is not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information.
